buytrafficonline.com 2017-12-31

# Privacy Policy - BuyTrafficOnLine.Com

**How BTOL Uses Your Personal Information**  
---  
This policy covers how BTOL treats personal information that BTOL collects and receives, including information related to your past use of BTOL products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.  
**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**  
BTOL collects personal information when you register with BTOL, when you use BTOL products or services, when you visit BTOL pages or the pages of certain BTOL partners. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address. When you register with BTOL and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. BTOL automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request. BTOL uses information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, and contact you.   
**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**  
BTOL does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested.   
**COOKIES**  
BTOL may set and access cookies on your computer. BTOL uses web beacons to access BTOL cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with BTOL products and services.   
**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**  
You can edit your BTOL Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time. New categories of marketing communications might be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the BTOL service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the BTOL Newsletter, that are considered part of your BTOL account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. You can delete your BTOL account by visiting our Account Deletion page.   
**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**  
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
